[
    {
        "question": "The word \"we\" in paragraph 2 refers to",
        "options": [
            "humans",
            "economists, sociologists, and politicians",
            "animals",
            "scientists"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "According to paragraph 2, how many degrees could the Earth warm up?",
        "options": ["2.5", "2.5 or 10", "10", "from 2.5 to 10"],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "According to paragraph 3, why should we stabilize GHG concentrations around 450-550 parts per million?",
        "options": [
            "to avoid the most serious effects of climate change",
            "to avoid all damaging impacts of climate change",
            "to mend the most damaging impacts of climate change",
            "to stop climate change"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What does \"which\" in paragraph 3 refer to?",
        "options": [
            "current concentrations",
            "that current concentrations arelabout 380 ppm",
            "380 ppm",
            "ppm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does the author mention Stephen Pacala and Robert Socolow?",
        "options": [
            "To introduce two researchers in the field",
            "To proves that researchers are working to reduce GHG emission",
            "To introduce one way to reduce GHG emission",
            "To introduce Princeton University"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What stabilization wedges are NOT mentioned in the passage?",
        "options": [
            "create environment-friendly materials",
            "capture and store carbon dioxide underground",
            "increase the use of renewable energy",
            "grow moretrees"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What does \"them\" refer to?",
        "options": ["researchers", "humans", "renewable resources", "wedges"],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best title for this passage?",
        "options": [
            "Arguments over Global Warming",
            "Global Warming and its Causes",
            "Global Warming Solutions",
            "Global Warming's Effect on Earth"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Sequestering\" has closest meaning to .....................",
        "options": ["Absorn", "Isolate", "Release", "Emit"],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does the writer mention ‚Äùdrawbacks\" in the last paragraph?",
        "options": [
            "To introduce the disadvantages of solutions in the following paragraph",
            "To emphasize the disadvantages of the solutions in the previous paragraph",
            "To recommend readers not to use the solutions",
            "To emphasize the advantages of the solutions in different contexts"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    }
]
